<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lupolupo</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="new_releases">\t\t\tNew Releases</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="open_source_license">Open Source License</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="subscribe">+ Subscribe</string>
    <string name="episode_no">#%1$d</string>

    <string name="empty">Empty</string>
    <string name="cover_image">coverImage</string>
    <string name="like_button">Like Button</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="please_try_again_later">Please try again Later</string>
    <string name="no_episodes_found">No Episodes Found</string>
    <string name="send_to">Share</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <string name="about_us_text">Welcome to LupoLupo!\n\nLupoLupo is a website that provides exclusive content intended to incite laughter and amusement… and hopefully make you laugh so hard you pee your pants.  So, if you are reading our content and you aren’t laughing your ass off, then maybe you aren’t stoned enough… cause when we thought up some of this stuff, we were totally baked and it was funny as F&amp;*k.  Just saying…\n\nYou’ll notice the site comes free of sign-ups and pop-up ads, so feel free to browse unencumbered.\n\nBut this is adult humor intended for adults, so if you are under the age of 17, you’ll want to avert your eyes and close this app.  Let’s face it, there are some things that you just can’t un-see.\n\nAnd to those of you who we might have poked some fun at… maybe even ridiculed (sorry, Donald), we apologize… but you got to admit some of it is too funny.\n\nAnyway, we hope you’ll enjoy our site.\n\nLupoLupo</string>
    <string name="contact_us_text">LupoLupo\nVenice Beach, California\n\nGeneral information and requests:	</string>
    <string name="contact_us_info_email">\t\tinfo@lupolupo.com</string>
    <string name="contact_us_feedback_text">\n\nAwards, Superlatives, etc</string>
    <string name="contact_us_feedback_email">\t\tfeedback@lupolupo.com</string>
    <string name="contact_us_text_complain_text">\n\nComplaints, Criticisms, and General Whining\n\t\tEat_Shit@lupolupo.com\n\t\tOkay… just kidding.\n\t\tYou can send those to </string>
    <string name="contact_us_text_complain_email">\t\tfeedback@lupolupo.com </string>
    <string name="as_well">  as well.</string>
    <string name="privacy_note">\nThank you for visiting www.LupoLupo.com, a general audience site presented by LupoLupo. (\"LupoLupo\"). Your privacy is important to us. As such, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site and among our network of affiliated websites and applications, which includes any online or mobile sites, applications or services owned, operated or offered by or on behalf of LupoLupo (each a “Site”, collectively the \"LupoLupo Sites\"). This Privacy Notice and the LupoLupo Terms of Use set forth the terms that apply to your access and use of the LupoLupo Sites. Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the LupoLupo Sites becomes published content available to the general public, which will be removed solely at our discretion, and which remains subject to our Terms of Use.</string>
    <string name="information">\nAt some LupoLupo Sites, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information (such as your full name or email address) in order to participate in various activities, such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. If accessing a Site from a mobile device, you may be asked to share your geo-location information, and identifiers designed to enable advertising on your device may be used by us or our service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners. You can turn off geo-location data collection at any time by accessing the privacy settings of your mobile device. Depending on the device, you may also be able to reset its advertising identifier by accessing the privacy settings.\nYou also can engage with our content, such as video, games, applications, and other offerings, on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook, and LupoLupo or third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, user files like photos and videos, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make, etc.) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with our content. Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.\n\nWe, our service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information when you visit the LupoLupo Sites. The information may be collected via cookies, log files, and web beacons (aka “clear GIFs”).\n\nCookies are text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters that are placed in your computer’s browser. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. However, once you choose to furnish a Site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the LupoLupo Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.\n\nLog files automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website (“Server Logs”). These Server Logs may include your Internet Protocol (\"IP\") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, device id, network speed, device type, network provider, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your visit, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.\n\nWeb beacons are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons may be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page.</string>
    <string name="use_information">\nWe will not use your personally identifiable information to send marketing messages to you without your consent or as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our terms of service, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us). We may use web beacons in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened.\n\nThe information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, services or customized experiences. If you register and create an account with a Site, the screen name you select as well as other content you submit to your profile (such as photos, comments, video content, or reviews) will be displayed publicly on the Site and may be reused and redistributed by us in our discretion.\n\nWe receive and store information you knowingly provide to us, including reputable third-party account registration information and/or log-in credentials. We also collect information you supply to us regarding your personal preferences and interests. If you access the LupoLupo Sites through Facebook Connect, you understand that some content and/or information in your Facebook account may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that third-party account information transmitted to the LupoLupo Sites is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with any or all of the information we specify or request, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some or all of our features.\n\nThe LupoLupo Sites include and run social media features, buttons and widgets. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the LupoLupo Sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.\n\n We use information collected via cookies, clear gifs, and web beacons to: (a) store your preferences; (b) understand Site and Internet use; (c) improve Site design and content; (d) manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the LupoLupo Sites; (e) monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page; (f) customize the content, offerings, or advertisements you see on the LupoLupo Sites; and (g) offer you products, programs, or services.</string>
    <string name="share_disclose">\nWe may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency\'s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the LupoLupo Sites and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.\n\nOur agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy notice and are not authorized to use the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.\n\nWe may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties to help them to understand the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, or functionality on the LupoLupo Sites. We may also share non-personally identifiable information with third parties to provide users with additional or more relevant product and service opportunities.</string>
    <string name="advertising">\nWe may use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and Site analytics, and to also assist us with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. The use of such technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy notice.\n\nAdvertising enables us to provide you with the content for which we are known. Our goal is to deliver advertising that is relevant to you. As part of this process we, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may collect information about your online activities across the LupoLupo Sites and other sites, and supplement such information with information from third parties, in an effort to make inferences about your interests and deliver to you advertisements targeted to those interests.\n\nWe may use reputable third-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to better understanding the behavior of our visitors and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on the LupoLupo Sites or other reputable third party websites to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies and web beacons). These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.\n\nAt this time, the LupoLupo Sites do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include \"do not track\" instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. Please consult the \"Help\" section of your browser for more information.</string>
    <string name="commitment">\nWe have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online. However, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy notice.</string>
    <string name="special_note">\nThe LupoLupo Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are accessing the LupoLupo Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the LupoLupo Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.</string>
    <string name="merger_sale">\nIn the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors\' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.</string>
    <string name="revisions">\nFrom time to time, we may modify this privacy statement. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. For revisions that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. Your continued use of the LupoLupo Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.\n\nThis Privacy Notice was last revised on January 1, 2017\n\nPlease contact LupoLupo with any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice or your personal information by visiting our</string>
    <string name="contact_page">Contact page.</string>

    <string name="welcome_note">\nThanks for using our products and services (“Services”). The Services are provided by LupoLupo. (“LupoLupo”), located at 13953 Panay Way, Suite 306, Marina Del Rey, CA 90292, United States.\n\nBy using our Services, you are agreeing to these terms. Please read them carefully.\n\nAdditional terms or product requirements (including age requirements) may apply. Additional terms will be available with the relevant Services, and those additional terms become part of your agreement with us if you use those Services.</string>
    <string name="about_our_site">\nThe LupoLupo Website allows for general viewing of various types of adult-oriented comics, images of adult-oriented content, including sexually themed images.  Accordingly, we encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the terms, conditions, and privacy policy of each other website that you visit.\n\nThe Website is for your personal use and shall not be used for any commercial endeavor except those specifically endorsed or approved by the Website.\n\nYou understand and acknowledge that you may be exposed to content that is inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable, and you agree to waive, and hereby do waive, any legal or equitable rights or remedies you have or may have against the Website with respect thereto, and agree to indemnify and hold the Website, its site operator, its parent corporation, their respective affiliates, licensors, service providers, officers, directors, employees, agents, successors and assigns, harmless to the fullest extent allowed by law regarding all matters related to your use of the Website.</string>
    <string name="use_of_material">\nYour use of the LupoLupo Site or Mobile App are for your own personal and non-commercial use only. You acknowledge that, as between LupoLupo and you, except for advertisements, LupoLupo is the sole owner of all content on the LupoLupo Site, including, without limitation, all applicable copyrights, patents, trademarks, trade secrets, trade names, logos, and other intellectual property rights thereto, as well as text, images, graphics, logos, audio, video and other material appearing on the LupoLupo Site (\"LupoLupo Content\"). The LupoLupo Site and LupoLupo Content are protected by the copyright laws and other intellectual property laws of the United States and are protected globally by applicable international copyright treaties.\n\nYou may download and print extracts from LupoLupo Content for your own personal and non-commercial use only, provided you maintain and abide by any author attribution, copyright or trademark notice or restriction in any material that you download or print. You may not use any LupoLupo Content for any other purpose without our prior written approval. Except as expressly authorized by LupoLupo, you are not allowed to create a database in electronic or paper form comprising all or part of the material appearing on the LupoLupo Site.</string>
    <string name="advertisement">\nIf you wish to use our content other than as permitted by these terms and conditions, please email us by using our</string>
    <string name="using_our_service">\nYou must follow any policies made available to you within the Services.\n\nDon’t misuse our Services. For example, don’t interfere with our Services or try to access them using a method other than the interface and the instructions that we provide. You may use our Services only as permitted by law, including applicable export and re-export control laws and regulations. We may suspend or stop providing our Services to you if you do not comply with our terms or policies or if we are investigating suspected misconduct.\n\nUsing our Services does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the content you access. You may not use content from our Services unless you obtain permission from its owner or are otherwise permitted by law. These terms do not grant you the right to use any branding or logos used in our Services. Don’t remove, obscure, or alter any legal notices displayed in or along with our Services.\n\nIn connection with your use of the Services, we may send you service announcements, administrative messages, and other information. You may opt out of some of those communications.\n\nSome of our Services are available on mobile devices. Do not use such Services in a way that distracts you and prevents you from obeying traffic or safety laws.</string>
    <string name="privacy">\nLupoLupo’s privacy policies explain how we treat your personal data and protect your privacy when you use our Services. By using our Services, you agree that LupoLupo can use such data in accordance with our privacy policies.</string>
    <string name="about_software">\nWhen a Service requires or includes downloadable software, this software may update automatically on your device once a new version or feature is available. Some Services may let you adjust your automatic update settings.\n\nLupoLupo gives you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the software provided to you by LupoLupo as part of the Services. This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the Services as provided by LupoLupo, in the manner permitted by these terms. You may not copy, modify, distribute, sell, or lease any part of our Services or included software, nor may you reverse engineer or attempt to extract the source code of that software, unless laws prohibit those restrictions or you have our written permission.\n\nOpen source software is important to us. Some software used in our Services may be offered under an open source license that we will make available to you. There may be provisions in the open source license that expressly override some of these terms.</string>
    <string name="modifying_and_terminating">\nWe are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove functionalities or features, and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether.\n\nYou can stop using our Services at any time, although we’ll be sorry to see you go. LupoLupo may also stop providing Services to you, or add or create new limits to our Services at any time.\n\nWe believe that you own your data and preserving your access to such data is important. If we discontinue a Service, where reasonably possible, we will give you reasonable advance notice and a chance to get information out of that Service.</string>
    <string name="warranties">\nWe provide our Services using a commercially reasonable level of skill and care and we hope that you will enjoy using them. But there are certain things that we don’t promise about our Services.\n\nOTHER THAN AS EXPRESSLY SET OUT IN THESE TERMS OR ADDITIONAL TERMS, NEITHER LUPOLUPO NOR ITS SUPPLIERS OR DISTRIBUTORS MAKE ANY SPECIFIC PROMISES ABOUT THE SERVICES. FOR EXAMPLE, WE DON’T MAKE ANY COMMITMENTS ABOUT THE CONTENT WITHIN THE SERVICES, THE SPECIFIC FUNCTIONS OF THE SERVICES, OR THEIR RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, OR ABILITY TO MEET YOUR NEEDS. WE PROVIDE THE SERVICES “AS IS”.\n\nSOME JURISDICTIONS PROVIDE FOR CERTAIN WARRANTIES, LIKE THE IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE EXCLUDE ALL WARRANTIES.</string>
    <string name="liability">\nWHEN PERMITTED BY LAW, LUPOLUPO, AND LUPOLUPO’S SUPPLIERS AND DISTRIBUTORS, WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR LOST PROFITS, REVENUES, OR DATA, FINANCIAL LOSSES OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES.\n\nTO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE TOTAL LIABILITY OF LUPOLUPO, AND ITS SUPPLIERS AND DISTRIBUTORS, FOR ANY CLAIMS UNDER THESE TERMS, INCLUDING FOR ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES, IS LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT YOU PAID US TO USE THE SERVICES (OR, IF WE CHOOSE, TO SUPPLYING YOU THE SERVICES AGAIN).\n\nIN ALL CASES, LUPOLUPO, AND ITS SUPPLIERS AND DISTRIBUTORS, WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE THAT IS NOT REASONABLY FORESEEABLE.</string>
    <string name="business_uses">\nIf you are using our Services on behalf of a business, that business accepts these terms. It will hold harmless and indemnify LupoLupo and its affiliates, officers, agents, and employees from any claim, suit or action arising from or related to the use of the Services or violation of these terms, including any liability or expense arising from claims, losses, damages, suits, judgments, litigation costs and attorneys’ fees.</string>
    <string name="about_terms">\nWe may modify these terms or any additional terms that apply to a Service to, for example, reflect changes to the law or changes to our Services. You should look at the terms regularly. We’ll post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. We’ll post notice of modified additional terms in the applicable Service. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen days after they are posted. However, changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. If you do not agree to the modified terms for a Service, you should discontinue your use of that Service.\n\nIf there is a conflict between these terms and the additional terms, the additional terms will control for that conflict.\n\nThese terms control the relationship between LupoLupo and you. They do not create any third party beneficiary rights.\n\nIf you do not comply with these terms, and we don’t take action right away, this doesn’t mean that we are giving up any rights that we may have (such as taking action in the future).\n\nIf it turns out that a particular term is not enforceable, this will not affect any other terms.\n\nThe laws of California, U.S.A., excluding California’s conflict of laws rules, will apply to any disputes arising out of or relating to these terms or the Services. All claims arising out of or relating to these terms or the Services will be litigated exclusively in the federal or state courts of Los Angeles County, California, USA, and you and LupoLupo consent to personal jurisdiction in those courts.\n\nFor information about how to contact LupoLupo, please visit our </string>
    <string name="these_terms_and_conditions_were_last_revised_on_january_1_2017">\n\nThese Terms and Conditions were last revised on January 1, 2017</string>
    <string name="there_is_no_any_featured_comic">There aren't any Featured Comic</string>
</resources>
